
        <dashboard version="2" theme="dark" hiddenElements="{&quot;hideEdit&quot;:false,&quot;hideOpenInSearch&quot;:false,&quot;hideExport&quot;:false}">
            <label>Useful Links and Guides</label>
            <description></description>
            <definition><![CDATA[{"visualizations":{"viz_Rdys1PUG":{"type":"splunk.markdown","options":{"markdown":"# Apps - Useful Tools\n\n### [Splunk SPL Examples](https://apps.splunk.com/app/3456/)\n\nThe Splunk SPL Examples app takes the Splunk Search Reference Guide and provides working examples of the commands, bringing the Splunk Search Reference Guide to life. The app is self contained, so for environments that do not have internet access, this app can still provide working examples of the search commands.\n\n### [Search Activity](https://apps.splunk.com/app/2632/)\n\nSearch Activity helps Splunk champions monitor users, grow usage, and understand personas. It provides metrics on use, organizational information, and adoption. Install it and answer all manner of Splunk questions, such as:\n* \"Who are my top users?”\n* “Who is running realtime searches?”\n* “How complete is my users' grasp of the search language?”\n* “How many errors do they receive?”\n* “How long does it take them to run a search, and over what timeframe?”\n\n### [CIM Validator](https://splunkbase.splunk.com/app/2968)\n\nThis Splunk app was developed with one goal in mind, reduce amount of time spent validating Splunk Common Information Model (CIM) compliance of technology add-ons (TA's). Use of this app simplifies validation process in several ways:\n\n-Identifies fields that are required, but missing\n-Validates data confirms to expected CIM values\n-Rapid prototyping and validation\n\n### [Splunk Dev For All](https://apps.splunk.com/app/4104/)\n\nWelcome to the Splunk Dev for All app! This app provides you with working snippets of content to make it easier to use SplunkJS, Splunk Python, and related capabilities such as some of the internals of Splunk. This app contains 30+ pre-packaged working code samples that you can put together to turn your Splunk dashboards into real applications with great user experience, more interactivity, and a richer feel. In addition, there are pointers to many places where you can learn more, or see the samples working in action."}},"viz_f3HKHtyR":{"type":"splunk.markdown","options":{"markdown":"# Purpose\n\nThis is a link of useful apps and dashboards to assist with using the platform. ","fontColor":"#ffffff"}},"viz_Vnw765Ts":{"type":"splunk.rectangle"},"viz_Q7LRLUeO":{"type":"splunk.rectangle"},"viz_Uv5qI3pE":{"type":"splunk.rectangle"},"viz_LKhaVz1d":{"type":"splunk.markdown","options":{"markdown":"# Apps \n\n### [Splunk Security Essentials](https://splunkbase.splunk.com/app/3435)\n\nGet started with Splunk for Security with Splunk Security Essentials (SSE). Explore security use cases and discover security content to start address threats and challenges.\n\nSecurity Content Library\nFind security content for Splunk Cloud and Splunk's SIEM and SOAR offerings and deploy out-of-the-box security detections and analytic stories to enhance your investigations and improve your security posture.\n\nCybersecurity Frameworks\nIdentify gaps in your defenses and take control of your security posture with automatic mapping of data and security detections to MITRE ATT&CK® and Cyber Kill Chain® framework.\n\n### [IT Essentials Work](https://splunkbase.splunk.com/app/5403)\n\nIT Essentials Work helps you correlate logs and metrics for each entity, and then use that information to observe and understand the performance of your infrastructure. The app helps you get started monitoring and analyzing IT infrastructures such as *nix, Windows, virtualization with out-of-the-box dashboards, and pre-configured performance metrics.\n\n### [Splunk Machine Learning Toolkit](https://splunkbase.splunk.com/app/2890)\n\nThe Splunk Machine Learning Toolkit App delivers new SPL commands, custom visualizations, assistants, and examples to explore a variety of ml concepts.\n\nEach assistant includes end-to-end examples with datasets, plus the ability to apply the visualizations and SPL commands to your own data. You can inspect the assistant panels and underlying code to see how it all works.\n\n### [Cloud Migration Assessment App for Splunk](https://splunkbase.splunk.com/app/4974)\n\nWelcome to the Splunk Cloud Migration Assessment App\nThis app is designed for existing Splunk customers interested in migrating to Splunk Cloud, our Software as a Service (SaaS) solution. The app will assess your current Splunk Enterprise deployment that is running on-premises or in a bring your own license (BYOL) model and provide guidance for your migration to Splunk Cloud.\n\nThe high-level assessment captured by this app will also provide data points to help our Sales Engineering and PS Teams scope your migration efforts, implement best practices, and prioritize your migration success. For more detailed information on the compatibility of your apps, use the Analysis Of SplunkBase Apps for Splunk.\n\n### [Splunk App for Chargeback](https://splunkbase.splunk.com/app/5688)\n\nThe Splunk App for Chargeback helps customers understand Splunk Virtual Compute (SVC) usage by business unit & department and uses the same exact SVC usage information provided in the customer's stack Cloud Monitoring Console (CMC) App.\n"}}},"dataSources":{},"defaults":{"dataSources":{"ds.search":{"options":{"queryParameters":{"latest":"$global_time.latest$","earliest":"$global_time.earliest$"}}}}},"inputs":{},"layout":{"type":"absolute","options":{"display":"auto-scale","height":1450},"structure":[{"item":"viz_Q7LRLUeO","type":"block","position":{"x":10,"y":830,"w":1160,"h":580}},{"item":"viz_Vnw765Ts","type":"block","position":{"x":10,"y":10,"w":560,"h":90}},{"item":"viz_Rdys1PUG","type":"block","position":{"x":20,"y":840,"w":1140,"h":570}},{"item":"viz_f3HKHtyR","type":"block","position":{"x":20,"y":20,"w":530,"h":80}},{"item":"viz_Uv5qI3pE","type":"block","position":{"x":10,"y":110,"w":1160,"h":710}},{"item":"viz_LKhaVz1d","type":"block","position":{"x":20,"y":120,"w":1140,"h":670}}],"globalInputs":[]},"description":"","title":"Useful Links and Guides"}]]></definition>
            <assets><![CDATA[{}]]></assets>
        </dashboard>